# André Meyer

Ribeirão Preto/SP | (16) 99245-6206 | andre.s.meyer@hotmail.com | https://www.andremeyer.com.br

## **Personal Profile**

I hold both Brazilian and Italian citizenship (Italian-Brazilian). Passionate about technology, at 34 years old, I am a curious self-learner and programming enthusiast. Always in pursuit of knowledge, I enjoy exploring various fields and reading about diverse subjects. In my free time, I like to go for runs, socialize with friends, read, work out, and watch good series.

# **Professional Experience**

# FRONT-END DEVELOPER | AK TECH | 07/2023 - PRESENT.

- · Creation of institutional websites.
- · Development of landing pages.
- · User interface design.
- · Integration with APIs.
- · Use of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, Redux, Next.js, WordPress e GIT/GITHUB.

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER | FREELANCER | 10/2022 - 07/2023.

- · Development of landing pages.
- · Creation of institutional websites.
- · User interface design.
- · Video creation and editing.
- · Creation of artwork for videos, thumbnails, and advertisements.
- · Use of HTML, CSS, JavaScript e React.

# CO-OWNER AND ADMINISTRATOR | WESHIPIT | 01/2015 - 12/2019.

- · Execution of administrative and financial routine activities.
- · Front-end and back-end maintenance and updates.
- · Database administration.
- · Creation of banners and product advertisements.
- · Use of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP e MySQL.

#### **Highlight Achievement:**

· Development of a cryptocurrency arbitrage bot in Node.js.

# TEST ANALYST | PEARSON EDUCATION DO BRASIL LTDA | 02/2013 - 12/2014.

- · Development of black-box, usability, performance, load and stress, and regression tests.
- · Development of automated tests in Java Selenium.
- · Use of Scrum Methodology.

# SUPPORT ANALYST III | PEARSON EDUCATION DO BRASIL LTDA | 05/2011 - 01/2013.

- · Technical support.
- · Team management.
- · Database updates.
- · Error and problem reporting.
- · Manual creations.

# **IT INTERN | EDITORA COC LTDA | 04/2010 – 04/2011.**

- · Registration system updates.
- · Responsible for the layout of digital booklets and COC vestibular materials.

### **Education**

EXECUTIVE MBA IN FINANCIAL MARKET AND CAPITAL MARKETS | UNYLEYA | 2022.

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE | UNISEB COC | 2014.

**Courses and certificates** 

2022 HTML.

Origamid.

2022 CSS: Flexbox, GridLayout, SASS and positioning.

Origamid.

JavaScript ES6.

Origamid.

2022 ReactJS.

Origamid.

2019 Git: become and expert in Git and GitHub.

Udemy.

2018 JavaScript e JQuery.

Origamid.

Web Design.

Origamid.

2014 PHP 7.

Softblue.

2014 SQL.

Softblue.

**Skills** 

Informatics: Website development.

WordPress. Git/GitHub.

React.js, Redux, Next.js HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

Scrum. Jira.

Microsoft Office.

English: Fluent – acquired during an exchange program in the USA from Feb/2020 to Jun/2020.